- My sister was taken.
I've been looking for Shari
over 20 years.
- Her real name is Laura Kerr.
- She goes by Lila.
- Cause of death was either
a stiletto or a switchblade.
- There may still
be a connection.
- There is a connection.
That was Shari on her phone.
Half the time. I think
if I turn around fast enough.
I'll see her there.
- We're gonna work
every lead on your sister.
but I need you to tell me that
you also know we're working
a young woman's homicide.
- I know what you're asking me.
okay?
I can work it.
- Your sister's married.
Her husband runs her.
Russ Kirby.
- Voight! It's him!
It's him! It's Kirby!
Go for Imani.
- I've got Shari. It's her.
- Who the hell are you?
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- You don't know who I am?
- We've met?
Do I get a phone call?
- You--no. you're not--
you're not being arrested.
You're--
You don't know who I am?
- I just said that I don't.
- Um. hey.
I'm your sister. Eva.
-
I don't have a sister.
- You don't remember before?
- Before what?
- Your name is Shari Imani.
You were taken
when you were six
by a man currently
calling himself Russ Kirby.
♪ ♪
- That's not true.
There must have been
some kind of a mistake.
- We have your DNA.
- I didn't give you my DNA.
- We got it from a beer bottle.
Found at your friend
Laura's trailer.
We tested it against samples
taken from our home
when you were six years old.
The tests don't lie.
- I wasn't taken
and I don't have a sister.
- Shari.
- I don't know why
you're calling me that!
- Not like this.
- Shari. we're sisters.
- Hank. tech got
a hit on Kirby's BMW.
They've got eyes. but they
haven't approached yet.
- All right.
have Ruzek and Kevin go.
- Got it.
Ruzek! Atwater?
♪ ♪
- The BMW was found abandoned
in the garage.
It was empty when we arrived.
- Can we confirm
he went into the station?
- Yes.
Got one witness. saw a man
matching your description
entering the station
six minutes ago.
- All right.
You three. you split up.
You cover the exits.
- You got it.
♪ ♪
- We need to check the footage
from when he entered through
the front eight minutes ago.
- Green hoodie. jeans?
- Yeah. White. 50s. built.
♪ ♪
- Hold on. Hold on.
Right there. That's him.
Can you follow him?
Follow him.
- On it.
- Do you have another angle
on this?
Can you zoom in?
♪ ♪
All right. Keep following him.
Hey. Kev?
- Go ahead.
- Kirby didn't
get on the train.
He went back outside.
I don't think
he's leaving without her.
- If you know
where he's headed.
it would be a huge help.
Look. anything you can tell us.
- What's he done?
- What Imani told you is true.
Russ Kirby took you
from your rightful home
when you were six years old.
We believe he also had
a hand in killing a young woman
named Laura Kerr.
She went by Lila?
- I'm sorry if
I overwhelmed you earlier.
- You didn't.
Look. I get that
you have DNA or something.
but I have a family.
Russ. he's my adoptive father.
He raised me.
He didn't take me from anyone.
- And he's your husband now?
- Hmm.
I know society doesn't get it.
I know that you won't get it.
But he's not my blood.
It's not illegal.
It's not wrong
in the way you think it is.
He's my family.
and he's done nothing wrong.
Nothing.
♪ ♪
.
- Why do I need a safe house?
- To keep you safe.
- From who?
- Uh. just a precaution.
There's two bedrooms upstairs.
Uh--
- Kitchen's in the back.
and there's some food there.
If you need anything else.
we can get it.
There's security
detail outside.
and I'll be there with them.
So if you guys. either of you.
need anything. you call me.
Okay?
- There's an extra set
of clothes in the drawer.
And the shower's
right over here.
I can turn it on for you.
I'll show you how
to turn it on. actually.
You just have
to turn this thing--
- You think I don't know
how to use a shower?
- Uh--
no. I just--
- That I didn't shower myself?
Have a room?
A life?
I wasn't a captive.
I'm not a victim.
- Okay.
- I--
I look like you.
- I'm gonna
take a shower now.
He might have gone to JoJo's.
- What?
- You wanna know where
Russ would go. right?
- Y-yes.
- We have a friend.
JoJo.
Russ might have gone to him.
- Okay.
Okay.
- It doesn't mean
I believe you.
But he can help
explain it to you.
♪ ♪
- Hold on a second.
I'm gonna put you on speaker.
All right. JoJo.
You got a last name?
- She doesn't know.
She said he's white.
maybe in his 30s.
They met him at a strip club
called Blazin'.
- She ever been to his house?
- No. but Kirby goes there.
She thinks it's by the river.
- All right.
we're running it now.
We'll call you.
♪ ♪
- Chicago PD!
- Hands! Hands! Hands! Hands!
Turn around! Hands!
- Turn around.
- Police! Turn around!
- Show me some hands.
- Turn around!
- Hands. Put your hands up.
- What?
- Put your hands up!
- Turn around!
- I didn't do anything.
- Freeze!
- Stop!
Where is he? Where is he?
- What? Who?
- Where is Kirby?
- Kirby?
- I am not playing with you.
- I don't wanna play!
I don't know.
I don't understand
why you're all here!
- Russ Kirby.
that's who we're looking for!
He was here?
- No. Why would he be here?
- JoJo. the quicker
you come clean--
- Why would he be here?
I haven't seen that man
in months.
- JoJo. you good?
- Hey. shut up.
- Is that why y'all are here?
He would never come here.
You can keep checking.
Check all you want.
Talk to anyone.
That man ain't here.
♪ ♪
.
- Sarge.
we checked JoJo's phone.
No contact. no sign of Kirby.
- Uh. same for inside.
All those guests. they swear
they haven't seen him.
- No indication why
he would come here?
- No.
- Okay.
Then we gotta consider
that Shari lied.
that this was meant
for us to waste time.
- But--no.
It must have been a mistake.
- It could be.
Certainly could be.
But it could also be that she's
identifying with her captor.
trying to protect him.
- I read her when
she told me about JoJo.
It was honest.
And before that.
it was like she recognized me.
She didn't lie knowingly.
And even if she did--
- It would be understandable.
I mean. we'd all
understand that. right?
Still. we need to
protect against it.
Look. Shari is a victim.
100%. yes.
She's also a co-offender
who beat her johns.
We could use that.
- What?
- To find Kirby.
We could press her.
- No.
Absolutely not.
That is a terrible tactic.
We are not doing that.
A woman that's been held
captive for 22 years.
you wanna press her?
- What do you suggest?
- Taking it slow.
like you said.
Okay? This was a big mistake.
She just needs time.
I'm gonna go back.
I'm gonna keep
working her slow.
- I told you Kirby wasn't here.
I'm not lying.
He was never here.
- I believe you.
If you help me find him.
this will be the last
you ever see of me.
- How am I supposed
to help you find
a man that wasn't ever here?
- How well do you
know him and Shari?
Sable.
- Not very.
- How about a young woman
named Laura Kerr?
She went by Lila.
- What's she got to do
with this?
- Bro.
We want Kirby for
aggravated kidnapping.
sexual assault with a minor.
and murder.
- I did some favors for Kirby.
I just hooked him up with blow.
He said he'd pay me back with a
free threesome from his girls.
Turns out it wasn't so free.
- He wanted cash.
- He shook me down
to pay for it.
That's his thing.
Johns pay him twice.
Once for the service.
and once to keep Kirby quiet.
You wanna find him?
He's probably
shaking someone down for cash.
- You got names?
- Imani.
- Yeah. this is Officer Ryan
working the safe house detail.
- Uh. what's wrong?
Did something happen?
- No. nothing.
It's--it's probably fine.
I just--I went
to give Shari lunch
and she didn't
answer the front door.
- Did she leave?
Did you see someone?
- No. no.
we've had eyes the whole time.
She's inside.
She's probably just sleeping.
She was great when
I saw her this morning.
She was asking all about you.
I'm sure she's okay.
but I just--
I thought you'd wanna know.
- Yeah.
Um. yeah. I-I'm on my way.
Shari?
Hey. are you in there?
Are you okay?
I'm coming in.
Shari?
Shari.
Are you okay?
- Why does it feel like
your voice is...
something that I've heard?
I feel like you look like me.
Like I--used to look like you.
I feel like I recognize
your voice. but...
That's not real.
- Why isn't it real?
- It can't be.
- No. it can.
Hey. it can.
I--I promise you
I would know you anywhere.
It is real.
- No.
No. no. no.
It's--it's--it can't be.
It's a lie.
There was never
another one of me.
There was never a family.
It was just me.
There wasn't another one.
♪ ♪
- You are my sister.
- There wasn't.
There wasn't.
There was just me and Russ.
Only me and Russ.
It's just me and Russ.
It's only me and Russ.
- It's okay.
It's okay.
- It's only me and Russ.
It's only me and Russ.
♪ ♪
- There was an us.
It was us once.
- I don't--
I don't believe you.
It's lies.
- No. it's not.
I can show you.
♪ ♪
.
- Only name from JoJo that
popped was Del Hoffman.
Works here.
According to JoJo.
Del's got a history with Kirby.
Kirby's shaken him down before
and Kirby needs a clean car.
This is where I'd come.
- Del Hoffman. Chicago Police.
-
- Hey. we need to talk to you.
- Where you going. huh?
- Hey. Whoa. whoa. whoa.
- Hey. relax. relax. relax.
What you running for?
- Tell Carla's big shot
boyfriend to put a ring on it.
She's bled me dry.
- This isn't about
child support.
What happened to your arm?
- Nothing. What's going on?
- What happened?
- Nothing.
It ain't no problem.
- Russ Kirby.
Was he here?
- Yeah. he was.
- Go.
- He was. He ain't now.
- When? When?
- Two hours ago.
He left. man.
He wanted money.
I don't have nothing.
- He did this to your arm?
- Yeah.
- Show me.
Show me!
- It's fine. It--
Idiot wanted money
'cause he was...
- Hold still.
- Leaving town with his sick
little minion bitch.
He used
her pink stiletto knife on me.
That don't magically
make me have money.
- Whoa. whoa. whoa.
It's his girl's stiletto?
- Yeah. she always carries it.
- Did you give him a vehicle?
Did you give him a car?
- Yeah!
- Kev!
- Yeah?
- Make and model.
- A blue Mazda pickup.
- He left here two hours ago.
Blue Mazda pickup.
Give him the temp tags.
Get out a BOLO. Find him.
Hey. Jen. it's Voight.
Listen. are you done with
Laura Kerr's autopsy yet?
Okay. good.
Can you do me a favor?
I want you to check Laura's
wounds for DNA transference
from Russ Kirby
and Shari Imani.
I know. Long shot.
Yeah. just call me direct.
Don't document.
Yeah. thanks.
Anything?
- Uh. BOLO's out.
Still going through PODs.
I got nothing yet.
but there's a lot to work.
- Yeah?
- Hey. are you alone?
- I'm with Shari.
- Am I on speaker?
- No.
- Wait. Why does it sound
like you're driving?
- I am.
- Why?
- I'm doing what
I said I would.
Okay? I'm taking it slow
and I'm helping her. remember?
I'm taking her to my place
to show her the stuff
I saved from when we were kids.
- Okay.
Eva. I--I need you
to bring her to the district.
- Why?
- Because I'm asking you to.
- Okay. I will.
After this. I will.
-
Okay. Eva...
I need you to remember
she's not six.
She can't be the girl she was
when she was six.
She's lived a life.
You know that.
-
- But I need you to bring her.
- I--I will. after this.
- Eva.
Eva?
Dante!
- You live here?
- Yeah.
This is all yours.
♪ ♪
That's the house we grew up in.
- Where's that?
- Montclair. New Jersey.
That's our dad.
And that's us.
We built this in the trees
and our mom hated it.
His name was Javan.
His friends called him Java.
He was a...
good man.
Never stopped
searching for you.
You were...
abducted on a Tuesday
right after school.
We didn't know.
We--we thought
you were at a friend's house.
Uh...
and--and you didn't come back.
It--it got late
and you just didn't.
You never came back.
Our parents quit their jobs.
and we searched for you.
We left Montclair six months
after you were taken.
And there was a lead
in Florida.
Tampa. and then St. Louis.
We went anywhere. Everywhere.
- They're gone now?
- Yeah.
I never stopped looking.
♪ ♪
You had a life.
This. all of this.
he took you from this.
- You and me?
- Yeah.
- I know where he'd go.
- What?
- He--he wouldn't
leave without me.
He'd wait because he knows
that I'd go to him.
- Wait. where?
- You'll kill him.
♪ ♪
- No. I don't have to kill him.
- Your team will kill him.
- No.
- The man who runs it will.
- No one has to get killed.
♪ ♪
- Then it has to be me and you.
I'll take you to him.
but only you.
Shari--
- Please?
Just us.
Me and you.
Like it always was. just us.
.
- Imani!
Imani!
Sarge.
Yeah. they're not here.
And I've been trying her cell.
She's not answering.
- I'm tracking it now.
- That's the building.
He'll be watching.
We need to use the side door.
- Why are you sure
that he's here?
- This is where I was
always supposed to meet him
if anything went wrong.
That was the plan.
-
Okay. Where?
- Basement.
Last unit on the right.
We gotta go through
the storage unit.
- No. no.
You're staying here.
- What?
- I'm police.
- You said--
- I said I wouldn't hurt him.
I said I would come by myself
with you. and I did.
I will not hurt him.
but you are not going inside.
- I'll be fine.
- No.
You are staying in this car
or we don't do this at all.
♪ ♪
The hell are you doing here?
I told you to stay in the car.
♪ ♪
Run. Shari. Run.
- Where the hell is she?
- She's close. Phone's close.
It's in one of these buildings.
- We need closer than that.
- Yeah. there's
a margin of error.
- All right. everybody.
split and search!
Let's go!
-
♪ ♪
- No.
- Use her cuffs.
- No. no. Shari.
- Don't call me that.
- Shari. no.
What are you doing?
Sh--Shari.
- Don't call me that.
- That's your name!
- It's not.
- Did anyone follow you?
- No.
- No? Or you don't think so?
- I have a team.
I have a team.
They'll track me.
They'll find you. and they'll
put a bullet in your--
- They won't.
I made her come alone.
- Grab her phone.
Turn it off. then the radio.
- No. no. Shari!
Shari. no.
Hey. Hey. look at me.
Look at me.
Remember that stuff
I showed you?
- I don't.
- Remember all those
things I showed you?
- I don't remember.
- It was us. Shari.
- I don't remember anything.
I was lying.
- Please.
- What is she talking about?
- Don't.
- Nothing. Where's the car?
- Don't avoid my question.
- Shut up! Don't talk to her.
Don't look at her.
- She made up lies.
It's not important.
- What kind of lies?
- You're the liar.
He's the liar.
- It's not important!
- Love.
- She said she was my family.
- I am!
I am.
- Go! Grab my bag.
It's in the back.
It's got the passports in it.
Go now!
- Shari!
Shari! Shari!
- Phone just turned off.
♪ ♪
- Down!
- I got everything.
Let's go.
- No. no. no.
Don't go with him.
- Let's go. Come on.
- Don't go with him. Shari.
- Hey! Hey!
Did you believe her lies?
Did you?
- No.
- Come here.
- Shari.
- Don't listen to him.
- Quiet!
Go. Take care of her.
Do it.
Hey. this is no different
than with Lila.
Go.
You gonna let this woman win?
Make her think you
believe all the lies?
Show me I'm nothing?
If you make me do this for you.
I'm not gonna be happy.
Do it now!
We're running out of time.
♪ ♪
.
- Shari.
Shari.
Hey. it's me.
♪ ♪
Shari.
-
- It came from the building
to the south of us!
- 5021 Ocean.
Shots fired at 78th and Turner.
I need some cars.
♪ ♪
-
- Imani!
- They're here. We have to go!
Come on!
- I'm here!
- Keep calling!
- They're getting away! Torres!
- Here. Here.
- Imani.
- Hey.
- Hey. Are you okay?
- They went that way.
-
Don't touch him!
- Sarge.
- Hey!
- Sarge!
- No. no. no. no!
It's enough.
Sarge. enough.
- No! No!
- Enough.
Sarge. enough
It's done. It's done.
- No! No!
No!
No. no.
♪ ♪
- I already answered
that question.
- Ma'am. can you look at me?
- It was Kirby who attacked me.
- And shot at you.
- Yes. okay?
Yes. Are we done?
- I just have a few
more questions that I--
- Look. I already
answered all of them.
Okay? You're just
repeating yourself now.
Please.
-
Okay.
- Hey.
I'm gonna get you uncuffed.
I'm gonna take you to Med
to get you checked out. okay?
Oh. my God.
No. no. no. no. no. no. no. no.
No. no. no.
Help. help!
Help. she's bleeding!
- Is that ambo still here?
Get me a car. Adam.
- Kim!
- Somebody call Med!
I need a paramedic.
I'm here. I'm here.
Eva. hey. Look at me.
- Get her up. Get her up.
get her up. get her up.
Please.
- Go. go. Up. up. up.
- Back the vehicles up!
We gotta make a hole!
Back the vehicles up!
♪ ♪
- 5021 Eddie.
notify Chicago Med
we're two minutes out.
Female. 28 years old.
attempted suicide.
Laceration to her wrist.
Massive blood loss.
- I was...
- What?
- I was never who
you thought I was.
I was always his.
- No.
No. no. no. You were never his.
You were never--
no. no. no. no.
Shari?
♪ ♪
You were part of me.
I was a part of you.
♪ ♪
We belong to each other.
- How is she?
- She's stable.
-
- She wanted to kill herself.
She tried to kill me.
He said it would be
just like Lila.
But you already knew that.
didn't you?
-
♪ ♪
Stiletto knife is hers.
ME found Shari's DNA
in Lila's wound.
There's no DNA transference
from Kirby.
His DNA didn't even pop
in that unit.
I've got him on cams.
Miles away at time of death.
♪ ♪
- Is it on paper?
She's--
She's not like us.
She wasn't born that way.
♪ ♪
Is my sister gonna
be charged with murder?
♪ ♪
Press play. Subtitles appear.
200+ languages. One app:  tryray.app